<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<knimeNode icon="./default.png" type="Manipulator" xmlns="http://knime.org/node/v2.8" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://knime.org/node/v2.10 http://knime.org/node/v2.10.xsd">
    <name>Table2XLog Converter</name>
    
    <shortDescription>
        This node converts a Data Table from KNIME platform into an event log port object. 
    </shortDescription>
    
    <fullDescription>
        <intro> This node converts a Data Table from KNIME platform into an event log PortObject. 
        CaseID, Event class, time stamp and format are mandatory to set up in the first table; 
        In table "Choose Attribute Set", other attributes for traces and events are set optional due to the need. 
        In Expert Choice, it lists the strategy to handle error, empty cells and the XFactory to create event log.</intro>
        
        <!--  still think sth options are not sol well defined -->
        <tab name="Standard Options">
        <option name="Case ID">Choose one column as caseID for the event log</option>
        <option name="Eventclass">Choose one column as eventID for the event log</option>
        <option name="Life Cycle">Choose one column as life cycle for the event log. If there is no such column, 
        choose the option NO AVAILABLE.</option>
        <option name="Time Stamp">Choose one column as time stamp for events in the event log.</option>
        <option name="Date Format">Set the format to parse the time stamp. 
         For example, if the date in "2009-12-31", to parse it, the Date format should be given "yyyy-MM-dd"</option>
       </tab>
       <tab name="Choose Attributes Set">
            <option name="Trace Attributes">Choose table columns as trace attributes. For all events with in one trace, they are supposed to 
            have the same values for each trace attributes. Else, it will omit this trace in the event log. Values from included columns
            will be shown as the attributes for each trace. Please make sure the columns chosen in "Standard Options" are included; else, it 
            will give the InvalidConfiguration Error. </option>
            <option name="Event Attributes">Choose table columns as event attributes. Values from included columns 
            will be shonw as the attributes for event. Please make sure the columns chosen in "Standard Options" are included; else, it 
            will give the InvalidConfiguration Error.</option>
        </tab>
        
         <tab name="Expert Choice">
          <option name="XFactory">XFactory implementation that is used to create the log. Some implementations might be more memory efficient, 
          consider changing this in case you import a huge log. Additional Conversion Options (Defaults are a good guess)</option>
          <option name="Error Handling">The strategy to stop conversion upon malformed input or try to import as much as possible.</option>
          <option name="Sparse / Dense Log">This affects how empty cells in the CSV are handled. 
          Exclude (sparse) or include (dense) empty cells in the conversion. 
						Some plug-ins require the log to be dense, i.e., all attributes are defined for each event.
						In other cases it might be more efficient or even required to only add attributes to events if the attributes actually contain data.</option>
		
           
         </tab>
       
    </fullDescription>
    
    <ports>
        <inPort index="0" name="Data Table">A Data Table in KNIME</inPort>
        <!-- possibly more input ports here-->
        <outPort index="0" name="Event Log">The event log converted from Data Table. </outPort>
      
    </ports>    
   
</knimeNode>
