<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<knimeNode icon="./default.png" type="Predictor"
	xmlns="http://knime.org/node/v2.8"
	xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
	xsi:schemaLocation="http://knime.org/node/v2.10 http://knime.org/node/v2.10.xsd">
	<name>Alignment-Based Replayer(Default)</name>

	<shortDescription>
		This alignment-based replayer accepts one event log and one Petri net as
		input and outputs the optimal alignments for traces after replaying
		traces on Petri net.
		In default mode, it sets unified cost for each move type.
	</shortDescription>

	<fullDescription>
		<intro>
			Alignment-based replay is the state-of-the-art technique in
			conformance checking.
			Alignments provide a robust and detailed view on the deviations. For each trace
			from the event log after replaying,
			there is one alignment corresponding to it.
			<dl>
				<dt>Sync move</dt>
				<dd>The classification of the current event corresponds to the
					firing transitions in Petri net.
					In this case, during replaying, both the trace and process model move
					to next comparison.
				</dd>

				<dt>Move on log</dt>
				<dd>The classification of the current event don't have any
					corresponding firing transitions in Petri net.
					During replaying, the trace moves forwards but the state of process model
					doesn't change.
				</dd>

				<dt>Move on model</dt>
				<dd>The firing transitions in Petri net has no corresponding event
					in the trace.
					During replaying, the model moves forwards but the state of the event log
					doesn't change.
				</dd>
			</dl>
			<br />
			With node in Default Settting, the costs are unified for one move
			type and can't be set for each move.

			<br />
			More information seen in the :
			<a href="https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/abstract/document/6037560">link</a>
		</intro>


		<option name="Event classifer">The classifier chosen to classify the event log.
		</option>
		<option name="Strategy type">
			The strategy to replay the event log on Petri net. It includes
			<ul>
				<li>
					ILP Replayer.
					<br />
					The repalyer calculates the optimal alignment based on ILP.
				</li>
				<li> Non-ILP Replayer.
				</li>
				<li>
					A*-ILP Based Manifest Replayer.
					<br />
					This replayer is reserved for performance checking. It generates
					the Manifest to wrap the alignments.
				</li>
			</ul>

		</option>

		<option name="Move on log cost">The unified cost for move on log in non-negative
			integer. In default, it is 1.</option>
		<option name="Move on model cost">The unified cost for move on model in non-negative
			integer. In default, it is 1.</option>
		<option name="Sync move cost">The unified cost for sync move in non-negative
			integer. In default, it is 0.</option>

	</fullDescription>

	<ports>
		<inPort index="0" name="Event Log">An event log as input</inPort>
		<inPort index="1" name="Petri Net">A Petri net as input</inPort>

		<outPort index="0" name="Alignment">
			The alignment result after replaying.
			<br />
			To benefit the analysis later, the corresponding event log and Petri
			net are also implictly included in the result.
		</outPort>
	</ports>

</knimeNode>
