<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<knimeNode icon="./default.png" type="Predictor"
	xmlns="http://knime.org/node/v2.8"
	xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
	xsi:schemaLocation="http://knime.org/node/v2.10 http://knime.org/node/v2.10.xsd">
	<name>Alignment-Based Replayer</name>

	<shortDescription>
		This alignment-based replayer accepts one event log and one Petri net as
		input and outputs the optimal alignments for traces after replaying
		traces on Petri net.
		With this node, the cost can be set individually for each move on
		log/model.
	</shortDescription>

	<fullDescription>
		<intro>
			Alignment-based replay is the state-of-the-art technique in
			conformance checking.
			Alignments provide a robust and detailed view on the deviations. For each trace
			from the event log after replaying,
			there is one alignment corresponding to it.

			<ul>
				<li>Sync move <br/>
				The classification of the current event corresponds to the
					firing transitions in Petri net.
					In this case, during replaying,
					both the trace and process model move
					to next comparison.
				</li>

				<li>Move on log<br/>
				The classification of the current event don't have any
					corresponding firing transitions in Petri net.
					During replaying, the
					trace moves forwards but the state of process model
					doesn't change.
				</li>

				<li>Move on model<br/>
				The firing transitions in Petri net has no corresponding event
					in the trace.
					During replaying, the model moves forwards but the
					state of the event log
					doesn't change.
				</li>
			</ul>
			<br />
			With this node, the cost can be set individually for each move on
			log/model.

			<br />
			More information seen in the :
			<a href="https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/abstract/document/6037560">link</a>
		</intro>

		<option name="Event classifer">The classifier chosen to classify the event log.
		</option>
		<option name="Strategy type">
			The strategy to replay the event log on Petri net. It includes
			<ul>
				<li>
					ILP Replayer.
					<br />
					The repalyer calculates the optimal alignment based on ILP.
				</li>
				<li> Non-ILP Replayer.
				</li>
				<li>
					A*-ILP Based Manifest Replayer.
					<br />
					This replayer is reserved for performance checking. It generates
					the Manifest to wrap the alignments.
				</li>
			</ul>

		</option>

		<option name="Move on log cost">The unified cost for move on log in non-negative
			integer. In default, it is 1.</option>
		<option name="Move on model cost">The unified cost for move on model in non-negative
			integer. In default, it is 1.</option>
		<option name="Sync move cost">The unified cost for sync move in non-negative
			integer. In default, it is 0.</option>

		<option name="Move on log cost table">
			The cost table for move on log with non-negative integer.
			<br />
			The cost table provides the ability to modify cost for each move.
			The unified move cost can assign the same cost to all items in the
			table.
		</option>
		<option name="Move on model cost table">The cost table for move on model in non-negative
			integer. </option>
		<option name="Sync move cost table">The cost table for sync move in non-negative
			integer. </option>

	</fullDescription>

	<ports>
		<inPort index="0" name="Event Log">Input port for an event log</inPort>
		<inPort index="1" name="Petri Net">Input port for a Petri net</inPort>
		<!-- possibly more input ports here -->
		<outPort index="0" name="Replay Result">Output replay result after replaying.
			It includes the alignment, implicitly the corresponding event log and Petri net as well.
			
		</outPort>

		<!-- possibly more output ports here -->
	</ports>

</knimeNode>
