<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<knimeNode icon="../category-manipulation.png" type="Manipulator" xmlns="http://knime.org/node/v2.8" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://knime.org/node/v2.10 http://knime.org/node/v2.10.xsd">
    <name>Filter Event Log by Frequency</name>
    
    <shortDescription>
        This node filters the traces based on their frequency in the event log.
    </shortDescription>
    
    <fullDescription>
        <intro>
        This node filters the traces based on their frequency in the event log. 
        Traces are always sorted based on the frequencies of the corresponding trace variants, and the most frequent trace variants are kept/removed. 
        The filtering strategy is used to determine whether to keep or to remove the most frequent trace variants. 
        The percentage of trace variants to be kept/removed is determined by the two filtering options: filtering type and and filtering threshold.
        <!--It has two strategies to filter. 
        One is on trace variant. Trace variant is a collection of traces with the same event classes sequence. 
        If the size of trace variant meets the condition, the trace collection will be added to the filtered event log; Else, the
        trace collection is disposed. 
        The other filter type is on the whole event log. The filter criteria is applied to the sum of trace variant. 
        Firstly, the traces in event log is sorted according to trace variant frequency in the descending order. 
        For example, given the threshold 0.8, and isKeep = true, the trace variants with higher frequency are summed to meet 0.8. 
        Their traces will be added to the generated event log.      -->  
         </intro>
        
        <option name="Keep">The filtering strategy. If this option is enabled, the traces/trace variants that meet the filtering threshold will be kept.
        Otherwise, the traces/trace variants that meet the filtering threshold will removed.</option>
        <option name="Trace Variant Filtering">The filtering type. If this option is enabled, the filtering will be applied on the trace variant level; i.e., trace variants that meet the filtering threshold will be kept/removed.
        If this option is disabled, the filtering threshold is used to set the percentage of traces to be kept/removed. </option>
        <option name="Threshold">The filtering threshold. It accepts both relative and absolute values (relative values between 0 and 1.0 and absolute integers greater than 1).
</option>
      
    </fullDescription>
    
    <ports>
        <inPort index="0" name="Event Log">the event log to be filtered</inPort>
        <outPort index="0" name="Event Log">the filtered event log</outPort>
       
    </ports>    
    
</knimeNode>
