<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<knimeNode icon="./default.png" type="Manipulator" xmlns="http://knime.org/node/v2.8" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://knime.org/node/v2.10 http://knime.org/node/v2.10.xsd">
    <name>Random Classify Event Log</name>
    
    <shortDescription>
        Random Classify Event Log node is supposed to classify the event log randomly based on trace variants. 
    </shortDescription>
    
    <fullDescription>
        <intro>This node assigns labels to traces. Labels are firstly defined in configuration nodes. 
        How to accept those labels?? How to give them values?? Another things is that, we must click on all the variants?
        So it's better to define the default values for this. 
        We need one label name, a set of possible values of this label. Define them as options.
        For one trace variant, we have the percentage to define the values, but also the number on it. 
        we can calculate the number for it. and decide the num to classify on it. Show the integer immediately.
        This is the setting, we need to know. But for each value, there is one percentage for it. 
        So we need to have the actionListener to adjust it. 
          
        The variants panel is always shown there. After we define the label and values, if we click on one variant,
        it should list the options to change the default percentage there. 
        
        After configuration, we need to remember the values for each variant!!! Event class lists and the defined percentage.
        When there are so many variants, we assign them already on the trace variants. 
        
        In another way, if there is not event log connected, we just check every trace variants and assign such values there. 
        So one question is, how to combine the chosen panel. 
        
        Our first task, is to create the ones without the trace variants panel.  
        
        </intro>
       
    </fullDescription>
    
    <ports>
        <inPort index="0" name="Event Log">Event Log to classify by randomly</inPort>
        <!-- possibly more input ports here-->
        <outPort index="0" name="Event Log With Label">Event log with labels after classification</outPort>
        <!-- possibly more output ports here-->
    </ports>    
   
</knimeNode>
