<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<knimeNode icon="./data_explorer.png" type="Visualizer"
	xmlns="http://knime.org/node/v2.12" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
	xsi:schemaLocation="http://knime.org/node/v2.12 http://knime.org/node/v2.12.xsd">
	<name>Data Explorer</name>

	<shortDescription>
		The Data Explorer node offers a range of options for displaying properties of the input data in an interactive view.
	</shortDescription>

	<fullDescription>
		<intro>
			<p>
			The Data Explorer node offers a range of options for displaying properties of the input data in an interactive view.
			</p>
			<p>
	        The node supports custom CSS styling. 
	        You can simply put CSS rules into a single string and set it as a flow variable 'customCSS' 
	        in the node configuration dialog. 
	        You will find the list of available classes and their description on our <a href="https://knime.com/css-styling">documentation page</a>.
	        </p>
		</intro>
		<tab name="Options">
			<option name="Show most frequent/infrequent values"> 
			If you check this option, the Nominal tab of the interactive view will create a column with the n most frequent nominal values and another column with the n most infrequent nominal values, for some number n that you select.
			If the selected number is equal to the total number of distinct values in a column, only one column with all values will be created. In all cases values 
			are listed in decreasing order of frequency.
			</option>
			<option name="Number of most freq./infreq. values">
			For any number n you select, the Nominal tab of the interactive view will list the n most frequent and the n most infrequent nominal values in separate columns.</option>
			<option name="Show median"> 
			If you check this option, the interactive view will show the median of the numerical values in the input data set.
			</option>
			<option name="Display Row ID in Data Preview tab"> 
			If you check this option, the Data Preview tab of the interactive view will create a column with Row ID of the data values.
			</option>
			<option name="Show missing values in histograms"> 
			If you check this option, the Nominal tab of the interactive view will show missing values as an additional bar in the histograms.
			</option>
			<option name="Enable automatic number of histogram bars"> 
			If you check this option, the Numeric tab of the interactive view will adjust the number of histogram bar of each numeric data column depending on the values occurring in the column. 
			If you uncheck this option, you will be able to enter a number of histogram bars used for all columns.
			</option>
			<option name="Title">
			Adds a title to the interactive view.
			</option>
			<option name="Subtitle">
			Adds a subtitle to the interactive view.
			</option>
			<option name="Enable global number format">
			Enables the same number format for all double values in the interactive view.
			</option>
			<option name="Decimal places">
			Specifies the number of decimal places for all values in the interactive view.
			</option>
			<option name="Max number of nominal values"> 
			Specifies the maximum number of unique values considered in one nominal column.
			</option>
		</tab>
		<tab name="Table">
			<option name="Display fullscreen button"> 
			If you check this option, the interactive view will enable option to enlarge the interactive view.
			</option>
			<option name="Number of rows for data preview">
			Determines the total number of rows displayed on the Data Preview tab of the interactive view.
			</option>
			<option name="Enable pagination">
			Enables spreading the table over several pages of the interactive view.
			</option>
			<option name="Initial page size">
			Determines the number of rows per page in the interactive view.
			</option>
			<option name="Enable page size change control">
			Enables changing the number of rows per page in the interactive view.
			</option>
			<option name="Selectable page sizes">
			Determines the page sizes you can select in the interactive view. Values need to be comma-separated.
			</option>
			<option name="Add 'All' option to page sizes">
			Adds the option of having all rows on one page to the page sizes you can select in the interactive view.
			</option>
			<option name="Enable selection">
			Enables selection of the data columns to be excluded from further analysis. 
			</option>
			<option name="Enable searching">
			Enables searching the data table.
			</option>
			<option name="Enable sorting on columns">
			Enables sorting of columns.
			</option>
			<option name="Enable 'Clear Sorting' button">
			Enables undoing any sorting by clicking on the "Clear Sorting" button.
			</option>
			<option name="Max number of nominal values">
			Maximum number of distinct nominal values per column. If the actual value is higher than the number entered in this field, 
			the interactive view will show a warning.
			</option>
		</tab>
	</fullDescription>
	<interactiveView name="Data Explorer View">
	<p>The interactive view consists of three tabs: a Statistics tab, a Nominal tab, and a Data Preview tab.  The Statistics and Nominal tabs sum up the information in each column. The user can then decide which columns to include in further analysis.</p>

	<p>The <b>Numeric</b> tab shows the main statistical properties of the numerical data, such as minimum, maximum, median (optional), standard deviation, variance, skewness, kurtosis, overall sum, number of zero values, number of missing values, number of not-an-object values, as well as positive and negative infinity values.  For each column, the node also calculates a histogram showing the value distribution.</p>
	 
	<p>The <b>Nominal</b> tab lists the main properties of the nominal values, such as the number of missing values, unique values, and top n most frequent and infrequent values.  In addition, for each data column there is a histogram showing the frequencies with which values occur in this column.</p>
	
	<p>The <b>Data Preview</b> tab shows the data selected for preview.</p>
	</interactiveView>
	<ports>
		<inPort index="0" name="Table">
			Table from which to compute statistics.
		</inPort>
		<outPort index="0" name="Filtered Table">
			A table with filtered out by user columns, chosen in the interactive view.
		</outPort>
		<!-- <outPort index="1" name="Statistics Table">
			Table with numeric values.
		</outPort>
		<outPort index="2" name="Nominal Histogram Table">
			Table with all nominal value histograms.
		</outPort>
		<outPort index="3" name="Occurrences Table">
			Table with all nominal values and
			their counts.
		</outPort> -->
	</ports>
</knimeNode>
