<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<knimeNode icon="./HM-icon.png" type="Learner"
	xmlns="http://knime.org/node/v2.8"
	xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
	xsi:schemaLocation="http://knime.org/node/v2.10 http://knime.org/node/v2.10.xsd">
	<name>Heuristics Miner</name>

	<shortDescription>
		This nodes implements the HeuristicsMiner to discover process models.
	</shortDescription>

	<fullDescription>
		<intro>
			This nodes implements the Heuristics Miner to discover process
			models.
			Heuristics Miner is an algorithm that acts on the Directly-Follows Graph,
			providing way to handle with noise and to find dependency between
			activities. An heuristics net or causal
			net is the output, which is a directed graph with activities as nodes,
			dependency interpreted as arcs and bindings.
			The Heuristics Net can be then converted into a Petri net.
			<br />
			The node Heuristics Miner shows the Heuristics Net as one internal
			result in View "Heuristic Net", while it
			outputs a Petri net after implicit conversion.

		</intro>


		<option name="Event classifer">The event classifier chosen to classify the event
			log.</option>
		<option name="All tasks connected">Every task needs to have at least one input and
			output arc,
			except one initial and one final activity.
		</option>
		<option name="Long distance dependency">Show long distance relations in the model.
		</option>


		<option name="Threshold: Relative-to-best">"Admissable distance between directly follows
			relations for an "
			+ "activity and the activity's best one. At 0 only the best directly
			follows "
			+ "relation will be shown for every activity, at 100 all will be
			shown."
		</option>
		<option name="Threshold: Dependency">Strength of the directly follows relations
			determines when to
			show arcs (based on how frequently one activity is followed by another).
		</option>
		<option name="Threshold: Length-one-loops">Show arcs based on frequency of L1L observations
		</option>
		<option name="Threshold: Length-two-loops">Show arcs based on frequency of L2L observations
		</option>
		<option name="Threshold: Long distance">Show arcs based on how frequently one activity is
			" + "eventually followed by another</option>

	</fullDescription>

	<ports>
		<inPort index="0" name="Event Log">An event log as input</inPort>
		<outPort index="0" name="Petri net">The discovered process model in Petri
			net</outPort>

	</ports>
	<views>
		<view index="0" name="Heuristic Net">Heuristic Net Visualization</view>

	</views>
</knimeNode>
